{
    "subject": "resource/Desperate_Teenage_Lovedolls",
    "predicate": "ontology/musicComposer",
    "object": "resource/The_Darkside",
    "human_readable": "The music composer of Desperate Teenage Lovedolls is The Darkside.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9618847966194153,
            "question": "Who composed the music for Desperate Teenage Lovedolls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9614117741584778,
            "question": "Name the musician behind the music for 'Desperate Teenage Lovedolls'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9263349771499634,
            "question": "What is the name of the composer behind Desperate Teenage Lovedolls' soundtrack?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.913515567779541,
            "question": "Can you tell me the composer of the Desperate Teenage Lovedolls soundtrack?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8605403900146484,
            "question": "Which artist created the music for the project Desperate Teenage Lovedolls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7779251337051392,
            "question": "Who is responsible for the music in the project 'Desperate Teenage Lovedolls'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7572319507598877,
            "question": "The Darkside is known for composing what musical work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7236841320991516,
            "question": "What is the name of the musical composition associated with The Darkside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7161287665367126,
            "question": "What project features music composed by The Darkside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5258657336235046,
            "question": "What musical work is linked to The Darkside?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The music composer of Desperate Teenage Lovedolls is The Darkside.",
            "html": "dbpedia_92_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What project features music composed by The Darkside?",
            "html": "dbpedia_92_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the musical composition associated with The Darkside?",
            "html": "dbpedia_92_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Darkside is known for composing what musical work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_92_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_92_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_92_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_92_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_92_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_92_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_92_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_92_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_92_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_92_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_92_48.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents mention \"Darkside\" contributing a song to the *Desperate Teenage Lovedolls* soundtrack, they don't explicitly state that they composed the entire soundtrack.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents mention any information about a music composer for the film or soundtrack titled \"Desperate Teenage Lovedolls.\" The documents discuss the band Dead Issue/Darkside, which contributed to the soundtrack but do not specify them as the main composers."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The band Darkside contributed only one song to the Desperate Teenage Lovedolls soundtrack, not the entire music of the film.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple bands contributed to the soundtrack including Darkside, Across The River, and Redd Kross.  Additionally, The Bags are mentioned as having a song featured in the film.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The information states that the band \"Darkside\" contributed a song called \"Right's Right\" to the soundtrack, but does not indicate that they composed the music for the entire film.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions that Darkside contributed a song to the Desperate Teenage Lovedolls soundtrack, but does not state that they were the music composers for the entire soundtrack.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}